No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Thanks for your help. No, no, no, no... it's nothing serious.
I've been working on the engine. I'm surprised I didn't call you tomorrow.
I'm late! I'm too late!
Yes...
I'll start with my ranking of the most moving Momokuro episodes!
The 4th place goes to
The first hug with Ms. Takagi!
Oh my God!
When I went to a live show as a back-up dancer for Momo Kuro when I was just a little kid in the 4th or 3rd grade, I told her that I liked her and she told me that she liked me.
I was a back-up dancer for Ms. Takagi at a live show, and I told her that I liked Momo Kuro.
Mimichan thanked me for that and gave me a hug.
I was just a tiny little flower.
I felt like Momokuro-san, who was watching me on that stage
It was like he was hugging me.
What? It's like that's impossible, isn't it?
Then, the third place
Arline and
Fourth place.
Then third place
Arline, Univa and Disney
This one, I'm sure you all really know this one.
When I was a member of Namie Women's First Union
Aaryn and I went to Disney and Univa together.
With Aaryn.
It's an unbelievable world line, isn't it?
When I think back to the days when I went to Monclo's shows as a guest...
I can't imagine going to Disney with someone who was on stage.
It was unthinkable to be talking about Disney with someone who was on stage.
I really enjoyed the show while chewing on the music, didn't I?
It was like having my favorite Disney and Aaryn together.
And Aaryn even bought us tickets.
He even bought us tickets and got us a hotel room.
We're supposed to do that, right?
Yes, but he was so skillful.
He was so good at what he did that we got it.
And everyone was like, "What? They were like, "What?
What? Oh, no.
Why is it too soon?
Really.
I thought you were very efficient and I respected you for that.
Disney and Universe were a lot of fun.
I had so much fun at Univa that we were all there the day before.
We had so much fun that we were all there the day before.
We had a lot of fun and ate dinner.
We had a lot of fun at the hotel.
It was so much fun!
It was a sleepover at Universe.
I got to stay over with Aaryn!
Isn't that amazing?
It was! Also, Arline lent Yuzu and Hana furisode (long-sleeved kimono).
Ha! Totally! I'm going to be 20 years old soon, so Arline lent me a furisode,
He said, "I have a lot of pictures, so I'll lend you one," and then he sent us pictures and asked us which one we liked,
He sent me a lot of pictures and let me choose which one I liked,
And then I thought that I might stain the furisode on the day of the wedding, right?
I thought it would never happen, so I put it on for a moment and put it away as soon as I could.
Arline let me choose the furisode that she was wearing on the day of the wedding, and she lent me a little bit of the furisode that she wore on the day.
I can wear the one Arline wore when she was 20 years old.
Yes!
We had a great pre-shoot. Thanks to Arline.
Second place
Jeez!
Now.
Now that's a phone call.
No, this is already really
I'm talking about now.
But who are these kind seniors?
I called on such short notice.
I was at work.
I was in the middle of an interview...
They called me back.
The four of us
in order
I was in the middle of a subject, so I'll put you guys on the phone.
Oh, no, no, no!
Kana-chan is on something on YouTube
I'll call you if something comes up during the filming
Hana-chan
Everyone's filming
Thanks for your hard work
Thank you for your hard work.
We're filming now.
Thank you all for calling me back.
I can't believe you guys called me back.
I can't believe you guys are talking to me now.
How kind are you? It's like...
I'm in a hurry.
No, I'm in the middle of an interview and I'm busy.
I can't, I'm busy with an interview.
I'm sorry," and then edit the line.
He's going to call me back.
Oh my God!
The four Momoqlo members...
All four of them are so kind and cute, and I'm always soothed by them, and I admire them, and I really respect them.
I have nothing but respect for them, and I've thought many times that I'd like to be like Momokuro-san.
I'm a really kind senior, and this phone call is something I'll be telling my grandchildren too much about when I'm a grandmother.
And the first place goes to
Arline's kindness.
You know, I'm already really indebted to Arline.
A long time ago, 3BJr. was a back-up dancer for Amemoncro's five major tours.
At that time, everyone was dancing on the street next to the stage.
And they were dancing in a totally dark place at first.
I didn't pay any attention to it.
We were just having a normal rehearsal.
During the rehearsal, Aryn said
The 3B Junior dancers on the aisle were dancing in the dark, so I couldn't see them.
It was too dark to see them.
"Shine a light on them," he said.
He told me to shine a spotlight on them.
"Shine a spotlight on them.
Isn't that crazy?
He's like a god.
What?
He's so thoughtful.
Aaryn is really...
It's something I would never have thought of.
And the back-up dancers...
He made sure they had a spotlight.
He made sure that everyone could see them.
Everyone at 3B Jr. was so moved by that.
It's amazing to have such a respected person so close to you.
I thought it was really great to have such a respected person so close to me.
I was really shocked at that time.
I have a short memory and forget things easily.
But I remember that moment vividly.
Aaryn was really cool.
He was number one.
But I really ranked them.
I mean, I ranked them all.
I mean, it's hard to rank them all.
They are really wonderful seniors.
We will follow Mr. Momoguro for the rest of our lives.
Yes, sir.
So I was all alone at a moment's notice...
But there were so many happenings...
I think it was the best thing that ever happened at Abechare.
I'm sure the number of times it's played will go up.
I was so happy and it was such a happy day for me too!
Yay!
Thank you so much for watching this video! This video is about how I'm working surrounded by wonderful seniors.
Thank you very much!
One person's comedy
Yes, I would like to do a comedy.
Governor Fukushima is urgently returning to Okinawa.